Guide to the Carl and Shelley Smith Mydans Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1930-1992; Series I; 33.83; (106 boxes)
  - Slides
    - Housed in Slide Boxes
      - Easter Island Dec 1964 - Feb 1965, Edited by Black Star 1982
        - Efford and Mathias; prime (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Efford and Mathias; rejects (weeded), undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 51)
        - Dentist & anthropologist; rejects (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Peter Beighton; prime (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Gabriel Veri Veri; rejects (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Rana Kao, Orongo and Bird Island; prime (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Encampment; rejects (weeded), undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 51)
        - Delivering and setting up the camp; also the encampment; duplicates (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Delivering and setting up the completed encampment; prime (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Delivering and setting up the camp; also: the encampment; prime (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Father Sebastian and the Church; duplicates (weeded), undated; (4 slide boxes) (Box 51)
        - Views from Poike; prime (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Views from Poike; rejects (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Elections; prime (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Panama Canal, ships (weeded), 1964 (Box 51)
        - Shore & ocean; prime (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Chileans; prime (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - "Cape Scott" & Pasquense boats; also Jelcho etc.; rejects (weeded), undated (Box 51)
        - Georges Nogrady Lab, undated (Box 51)
      - Venezuela: People and scenes at Caracas, before Angel Falls climb, 1965 (Box 51)
      - Angel Falls, undated (Box 51)
      - Carl Mydans on the Auyantepui climb in Venezuela by George de Steinheil, undated (Box 51)
      - Venezuela, Rockefeller Ranch (empty), 1966 (Box 51)
      - Fishing for stripers off Montauk, 1966 (Box 51)
      - Virgin Islands, 1967 (Box 51)
      - Honolulu, on return from Vietnam, 1968 (Box 51)
      - Japan
        - MacArthur -- Alton Toby's murals New Rochelle, 1965 September 19 (Box 52)
        - Nara, 1969 June (Box 52)
        - Ancient capital grounds, 1969 June 27-29 (Box 52)
        - Heijo Palace site; Hokke-ji, Todai-ji, Kofuko-ji, Yakushi-ji pagoda, 1969 June (Box 52)
        - Defense force march-past, 1969 November 1 (Box 52)
        - Temple on Lake Biew Ishiyama-dera & Mii-dera, 1969 November 3 (Box 52)
        - Bamboo: Japan (Rejects), 1969 November 4; (4 slide boxes) (Box 52)
        - Protest marches: on Sato's departure, 1969 November 16 (Box 52)
        - Temples in Nara and scenes at Ise shrine and at Mii-dera on Lake Biwa, 1969-1970 (Box 52)
        - Japan from a train Window ("The Hikari"), 1969-1970 (Box 53)
        - Hikari, Kyoto to Tokyo, 1970 March 26 (Box 53)
        - Nara: The Shosoin Treasure-House, 1970 March 26 (Box 53)
        - Sebornia Yacht Club and sailing with Sy Janow near Zushi/Aburatsubo, 1970 August 29-30 (Box 53)
        - Nara: General scenes, 1970 November 1 (Box 53)
        - Nara: Todaiji; Sangatsu-do, 1970 November 1 (Box 53)
        - Nara: Todaiji, 1970 November 1 (Box 53)
        - Nara: Toshodaiji, 1970 November 2 (Box 53)
        - Nara: Shin Yakushiji, 1970 November 2 (Box 53)
        - Conversions: Uji Bridge, Ise Shrine. See box no. 2 of 1-2, 1970 November 2 (Box 53)
        - Ise: Torii, bridges, tourists, scenic shrines; No. 1 (1-2), 1970 November 2 (Box 53)
        - Ise: No. 2, 1970 November 2 (Box 53)
        - Okinawa Day, Tokyo, 1970 (Box 53)
        - Mt. Fuji and countryside on clear day from Hikiri, 1970 November 11 (Box 53)
      - Hong Kong
        - Cheung Chau Island, 1969 March 26 (Box 54)
        - Spirit of Tai Pak: Village Hong Kong, 1970 June 15; (2 slide boxes) (Box 54)
        - Hong Kong fruit stalls, 1970 (Box 54)
        - Pop Art in Asian signs and shop fronts, undated (Box 54)
        - Market Scenes (For Fortune), undated (Box 54)
        - Hong Kong, 1970 June; (2 slide boxes) (Box 54)
        - Sheraton hotel, Hong Kong, 1973 August (Box 54)
      - Warburg Estate, 1971-1972; (4 slide boxes) (Box 55)
        Includes slides of Byram River waterfall, Warburg cottage, and Canada geese on Warburg pond.
      - Moorea
        - Bali Hai, Shelley and friends, 1971 (Box 55)
        - Bali Hai, 1971 March (Box 55)
        - First Visit, No. 1, Choice for story, undated (Box 55)
        - Fishing Outrigger at sunset, 1971 March (Box 55)
        - George, Christina, Donald Logue; Shelley, 1971 March (Box 55)
        - The Kellums, 1971 March (Box 55)
        - Papetoai and Cooks Bays, 1971 March 5 (Box 55)
        - Scenes, activities, life, 1971 March (Box 55)
        - Tahiti thatch, 1971 March (Box 55)
        - Tahiti Mara's, Moorea: believed to be places of worship of Polynesians on Moorea. Rain forest has been cleared away, mostly Mape trees; Medford Kellum, Ross Curtis, Shelley, 1971 March 5 (Box 55)
        - Willie Lowgreen story, 1971 March; (2 slide boxes) (Box 55)
        - Projection Drum 1 and 2, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 55)
      - Micronesia
        - Guam, 1972 March (Box 55)
        - Majuro, 1972 March (Box 55)
        - Saipan, 1972 March (Box 55)
        - Truk; Ponape; signs, 1972 March (Box 55)
      - POW Return, Clark Air Force Base, Philippines: No. 1, 1973 February (Box 55)
      - Bali and Borobudur, Indonesia
        - Bali, Shelley and Personal, 1968 September (Box 55)
        - Craftsmanship, Upud, 1969 September (Box 55)
        - Tooth filing ceremony Upud. Preparing festival food: withheld from Blackstar: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1969 September 27; (2 slide boxes) (Box 55)
        - Upud region: No. 1 - No. 3 (1-3), 1969 September; (3 slide boxes) (Box 55)
          Includes slides of rain forest roots above ground.
        - Paddy Fields, Ducks & duck boys, Upud., 1969 September, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Blessing of Holy Procession, 1969 September (Box 55)
        - Modern Balinese painting, Upud, 1969 September (Box 55)
        - Indonesia: Makassar, Col. Sjamsuddin; jackfruit tree (durian tree) planted for us; some scenes of boats, 1969 September (Box 55)
        - Galungan Festival decorations/activities: No. 1, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Mengwi Village Festival, 1973 July 26 (Box 55)
        - Stone carvings and stone temple decorations, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Ida Bagus Gelodod - Mask maker, Mas, Bali, 1973 July - August (Box 55)
        - Weaving and silver craftsmanship, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Stone carving restoration, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - General scenes, also crossing Bali Straits to Java, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Drama, dance and Gamelan: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1973 July; (2 slide boxes) (Box 55)
        - Boy stone-carvers, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Bali: General scenes, paddies, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Bali: general, 1973 July - August (Box 55)
        - Palm festival decorations, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Rice festival decorations, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Donald Friend, 1973 July (Box 55)
        - Painters, 1973 August (Box 55)
        - Wood carvers: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1973 August; (2 slide boxes) (Box 55)
        - Amri Yahya, artist, Yogyakarta, 1973 August (Box 56)
        - Indonesia: Surabaya & Yogyakarta, 1973 August (Box 56)
        - Borobudur, Indonesia: No. 1 - No. 5 (1-5), 1973 August; (5 slide boxes) (Box 56)
        - Bali: 42 numbered transparencies on Bali, withheld from Blackstar, 1973 September (Box 56)
        - Pendjor decorations, 1973 September (Box 56)
        - Bali and Jogjakarta by Shelley Mydans, 1975 October (Box 56)
        - Craftsmanship (withheld from Black Star), 1983 March (Box 56)
        - Bali: General selection of scenes and subjects, withheld from Black Star, undated (Box 56)
        - Transparencies with numbered frames, Leyaks of Bali, No. 1 and No. 2, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 57)
      - Japanese in Southeast Asia: their presence in Thailand: No. 1 - No. 3 (1-3), 1970; (4 slide boxes) (Box 57)
        Includes slides of Bangkok while on shoot.
      - Japanese Peace Corps in Philippines: shiitake mushroom: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1970; (2 slide boxes) (Box 57)
      - Overseas Chinese
        - Macau: Stanley Ho, No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - Bangkok, Thailand, 1970 (Box 58)
        - Bangkok, Thailand: Chin Sophonpanich, 1970 (Box 58)
        - Thailand city of Cholburi, 75 Kil. S.E. of Bangkok: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1970; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - Manila, Philippines, 1970; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - Philippines: The SyCips, No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - S.K. Seah, Rank Xerox Corp., undated (Box 58)
        - Djakarta, Indonesia, 1970; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - Indonesia. The town of Tjibinong (Fortune called it) I listed it as Djatinegara, 1970 (Box 58)
        - Penang, Malaysia: Kuok Hock Nien (Robert Kuok), 1970 (Box 58)
        - Singapore: Lien Ying-chow (George Lien), 1970 (Box 58)
        - Singapore: Robin Loh, shipping and other major enterprises, 1971 February 23 (Box 58)
        - Singapore: Run Run Shaw, undated (Box 58)
        - Singapore: Runme Shaw, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - Singapore: Tiger Balm and Aw Cheng Chye, undated (Box 58)
        - Singapore, 1970; (4 slide boxes) (Box 58)
          Includes slides of Robin Loh, Barter Wharf, Jurong, Shelley, Ebba Kraar.
        - Catalogue of faces we used, 1970 (Box 58)
        - Hong Kong: Y.H. Kwong, No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - Hong Kong: Ping Yuan Tang, undated (Box 58)
        - Hong Kong, Wanchai, 1971; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
      - Singapore-Bangkok Train Story
        - Views from the Train, No. 1 - No. 2, 1970 July; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - Platform scenes, No. 1 - No. 2, 1970 July; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - Inside train, 1970 July (Box 58)
        - Locomotives, 1970 July (Box 58)
        - Singapore, 1970 July (Box 58)
        - Penang, 1970 July; (2 slide boxes) (Box 58)
        - Kuala Lumpur, 1970 July (Box 58)
        - Bangkok, Thailand, temples, 1970 July (Box 58)
        - Malacca, 1970 July (Box 58)
        - Rubber: Malaysia; Train Story, 1970 July (Box 59)
        - Frames sent to Travel and Leisure, undated; (3 slide boxes) (Box 59)
      - Singapore
        - Prime Minister Lee Kuan Yew, 1970 November 17 (Box 59)
        - Singapore, 1970 December 1 (Box 59)
        - Singapore Harbor from Dragon Mansions, 1973 April-May; (2 slide boxes) (Box 59)
        - General views, 1973 May-June (Box 59)
        - Kusu Island, fertility pilgrimage, Festival of Deepavali, No. 1 - No. 2, 1973 October 20; (2 slide boxes) (Box 59)
        - Sengkang Island, Singapore Harbor waters, Kampong of Singapore, 1973 April 22 (Box 59)
        - Singapore for Fortune, 1974 January; (9 slide boxes) (Box 59)
          Includes slides of skyline, harbor, views from DBS building, board meeting, Howe Yoon Chong, Chairman and President, Dev. Bank of Singapore.
        - Changi Prison visit, 1974 June 8 (Box 59)
          Includes slides of Shelley with George Thomson.
        - Housing, 1974 September (Box 59)
        - Shipbuilding, Jurong Shipyard Ltd., 1974 September (Box 59)
        - Jurong, textile, 1974 September (Box 59)
        - Jurong, "Starlight Timber Products Ltd.", 1974 September (Box 59)
        - Northern Electric, "Contempra" telephone at Mandarin Hotel, 1974 December 28-29 (Box 59)
        - Boat Quays and river activities and scenes, 1974-1975; (3 slide boxes) (Box 59)
        - Shenton Way, 1974-1975 (Box 59)
        - Views from Fullerton Building, 1974-1975; (2 slide boxes) (Box 59)
        - Showa Maru, Tanker, Singapore: No. 1 - No. 2, 1975 January 21; (2 slide boxes) (Box 59)
        - From High Street Shopping Center Building, 1975 January-February (Box 59)
        - River boat trip scenes, also harbor skyline, 1975 February; (2 slide boxes) (Box 59)
        - Views from our bedroom window, lens tests, 1975 March 25 (Box 59)
        - Singapore-Bangkok Train Trip, 1975 August; (2 slide boxes) (Box 59)
        - New harbor skyline from North Boat Quay; also view from Cavanaugh Bridge, undated (Box 59)
        - Lee Kuan Yew, 1975 October (Box 59)
        - Beginnings and incomplete selection of Kraar/Mydans Geo Story, 1979 (Box 59)
        - All this box returned by Blackstar, Prime Singapore slides, 1987 August (Box 60)
        - J.Y. Pillay, Singapore Airlines Chairman, undated (Box 60)
        - General, also train trip, undated (Box 60)
        - People, undated (Box 60)
        - Chinatown: Carousel selections of 106 frames, undated; (3 slide boxes) (Box 60)
        - Rubber Tropical Produce Company, undated (Box 60)
        - Views from Hilton Towers, undated (Box 60)
      - Sydney, Australia, 1971 February (Box 61)
      - Honolulu, 1972 March (Box 61)
      - Kent State University, 1972 April (Box 61)
      - Enfield, New Hampshire, 1972 August-October; (3 slide boxes) (Box 61)
        Includes slides of Mitri the Blacksmith, air view of Enfield and Lake Mascoma.
      - American Scene: N. England: RR Station, Kingston, Rhode Island; "No Bare feet Please," Auction notice, N. England house/barn, Enfield, New Hampshire, 1972 August (Box 61)
      - Singapore's Chinatown
        - Chinatown at night; mostly Trengganu St.: No. 1 - No. 3 (1-3), 1975 January; (3 slide boxes) (Box 62)
        - Chinatown at night; Teo Chew Wayang; North boat quay at Clarke St. and Tan Tye Place, 1975 January (Box 62)
        - Sago Lane Funeral ceremonies (night): No. 1 - No. 4 (1-4), 1975 January; (4 slide boxes) (Box 62)
        - Thong Tai Medical Institute (77 years old), 1975 February (Box 62)
        - Chinatown markets; Trengganu, Smith Street and other markets, 1975 February (Box 62)
        - Pickering St. Coffin makers and other scenes: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1975 February; (2 slide boxes) (Box 62)
        - The last pictures of the raising of Chinatown just before leaving Singapore; also, few figures of Tiger Balm Gardens, 1975 November (Box 62)
        - 40 Singapore color slides with captions, undated (Box 62)
        - Temples: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 62)
        - Long views and match-up frames, undated (Box 62)
        - Market scenes, etc.; fish, undated (Box 62)
        - River and boat quay scenes, undated (Box 62)
        - Craftsmen, undated (Box 62)
        - Services, hospitals, herb stores, etc., undated (Box 62)
        - Entertainment, wayang, mahjong, etc., undated (Box 62)
        - Food, eating, fish, undated (Box 62)
        - Street scenes, etc., undated (Box 62)
        - People, undated (Box 62)
        - Temples, undated (Box 62)
        - Funerals, undated (Box 62)
        - OCBC Building overshadows Chinatown at Church St., undated (Box 62)
        - Herb shops, undated (Box 62)
        - Upper Cross Rd. being emptied for destruction, undated (Box 62)
        - Telok Ayer St., undated (Box 62)
        - General views, undated (Box 62)
        - Chinatown markets; Trengganu, Smith Street and others, undated (Box 62)
        - Street views: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 62)
        - Sago Street, undated (Box 62)
        - Views from United Overseas Bank Bld., undated (Box 62)
        - Club St., undated (Box 62)
        - Views from National Devel. Building, undated (Box 62)
        - Banda St.: No. 1, undated (Box 62)
        - Craftsmen, artisans, activities: No. 1 - No. 3 (1-3), undated; (3 slide boxes) (Box 62)
        - People's Park and Temple St. etc., undated (Box 62)
        - Activities at night: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 62)
        - Reptile Butchers, Trengganu St., undated (Box 62)
        - Oil Palm and making of palm oil, 1973; (31 slide boxes) (Box 63)
          Includes slides of plantation, nursery, mill, pollination, harvesting, people/faces, port & shipping.
      - Malaysia
        - Pemanggil Island, 1973 June 22 (Box 63)
        - Rawa Island, 1973 June 24 (Box 63)
        - General Motors Harimau in the Johore Bahru Area: No. 1 - No. 3, 1973 November 19; (3 slide boxes) (Box 63)
        - Langkawi, 1973 December; (3 slide boxes) (Box 63)
          Includes slides of boats, shops, animals, and things; pink buffalo; vistas, people, our party.
        - Kuala Perlis, 1973 December (Box 63)
        - Kuala Lumpur: general for Time ad selection, 1974 August (Box 63)
        - Cameron Highlands, at "Moonlight," T. G. and Helen Ling's, 1974 December (Box 63)
        - Tamen Nagara: Aborigines: No. 1 - No. 2, 1975 May; (2 slide boxes) (Box 63)
        - Tamen Nagara: Encampment (Box 63)
        - Tamen Nagara: Jungle walk and from the blind: No. 1 - No. 2, 1975 May; (2 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Tamen Nagara: People, 1975 May (Box 64)
        - Tamen Nagara: returned by Ivor Kraal in Oct 1980, undated (Box 64)
        - Tamen Nagara: River scenes, 1975 May (Box 64)
        - Tamen Nagara: Swimming, 1975 May (Box 64)
        - Malaysia to Blackstar, 1987 August (Box 64)
      - Burma
        - Pagan: No. 2, 1974 February; (2 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Pagan, Sunrise and sunsets, 1974 February (Box 64)
        - Pagan, temples and pagodas: No. 1 - No.4, 1974 February; (4 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Pagan, miscellany, people today, 1974 February (Box 64)
        - Pagan, market scenes; also carts and wagons & carriages: No. 1 and No. 2, 1974 February; (2 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Mandalay: No. 1 and No. 2, 1974 February; (2 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Rangoon: No. 1 and No. 2, 1974 February; (2 slide boxes) (Box 64)
      - Small Boat Building: Hong Kong: American Marine Ltd.
        - Keel and deckhouse, 1974 April (Box 64)
        - Frames: No. 1 and No. 2, 1974 April; (2 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Caulking and painting, 1974 April (Box 64)
        - Hand-crafting: No. 1 - No. 3, 1974 April; (3 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Interiors, 1974 April (Box 64)
        - Plugging, 1974 April (Box 64)
        - Finished boats, 1974 April (Box 64)
      - India
        - Agra region, 1974 October (Box 64)
        - Agra: Taj Mahal, 1974 October - November (Box 64)
        - New Delhi: No. 1 - No. 2, 1974 October; (2 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Jaipur & region, 1974 October (Box 64)
        - Amber Palace near Jaipur, 1974 October (Box 64)
        - Benaras: No. 1 - No. 2, 1974 November; (2 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Animals, wagons, etc.: No. 1 - No. 3, 1974 October - November; (2 slide boxes) (Box 64)
        - Final culls out of rejects, 1974 November (Box 65)
        - General or uncaptioned scenes, 1974 October - November (Box 65)
      - Kashmir
        - No. 1 - No. 6, 1974 October; (6 slide boxes) (Box 65)
          Includes slides of old city (3rd bridge area).
        - Kashmir: Three boxes for projection (two of them on the lake and canals): No. 1 - No. 3, undated; (3 slide boxes) (Box 65)
      - Nepal
        - Nepal: No. 1 - No. 2, 1974 November; (2 slide boxes) (Box 65)
        - Durban Square, Patan, near Kathmandu, 1974 November (Box 65)
        - Village of Bhadgaon near Kathmandu, 1974 November (Box 65)
        - Village of Kirtipur near Kathmandu, 1974 November (Box 65)
      - Baguio, Philippines, tropical fruit, 1974 December; (2 slide boxes) (Box 65)
      - East Africa Safari
        - East Africa Safari, 1975 (Box 65)
        - Lake Amboseli at foot of Kilimanjaro, 1975; (2 slide boxes) (Box 65)
        - Lake Manyara National Park, 1975; (3 slide boxes) (Box 65)
        - Mara Game Reserve, 1975; (3 slide boxes) (Box 65)
        - Serengeti National Park, Tanzania, 1975; (5 slide boxes) (Box 65)
        - Olduwai Gorge, Kenya, 1975 (Box 65)
      - Egypt: Luxor and Cairo, 1975 November (Box 65)
      - Egypt, undated (Box 65)
      - Israel, 1975 November - December (Box 65)
      - Jean and Milton Rosenbaum's Home, 1975 December (Box 65)
      - Sri Lanka
        - Galle, 1975 (Box 65)
        - Hikkaduwa, also boats, 1975 (Box 65)
        - Perandeniya: Sri Lanka's Royal Botanic Gardens, near Kandy, undated; (7 slide boxes) (Box 65)
      - U.S. Elections: 1976
        - Jimmy Carter electioneering, 1976; (4 slide boxes) (Box 66)
        - Democratic Convention, 1976 July 13-15 (Box 66)
        - Republican Convention, 1976 August; (9 slide boxes) (Box 66)
        - Presidential Inauguration, 1977 January 20; (2 slide boxes) (Box 66)
      - Plains and Archery, Georgia
        Includes captions for Plains and Archery, Jimmy Carter's birthplace and the town in which he grew up.
        - Miscellany, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - "Colored" section, Plains, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Billy Carter's gas station and home; also his son Buddy Carter, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Plains/Archery copies of frames in set, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Farmhouse and land near Plains air field, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - People, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Hugh Carter's antique store with Alton & Hugh, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Hugh Carter: home and worm farm and portraits, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Churches, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Air views, Atlanta to Plains. Poor because of colored plexiglass, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Main Street, Plains, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Houses in Plains, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Jimmy Carter's house (Plains) and road-block, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Houses on the land: No. 1 - No. 2, 1976 December 18-24; (2 slide boxes) (Box 66)
        - The land: No. 1 - No. 2, 1976 December 18-24; (2 slide boxes) (Box 66)
        - Archery: No. 1 - No. 2, 1976 December 18-24; (2 slide boxes) (Box 66)
        - Cemeteries, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Haunted House, Archery, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - General views & miscellany: No. 1 - No. 2, 1976 December 18-24; (2 slide boxes) (Box 66)
        - Railway Station, 1976 December 18-24 (Box 66)
        - Old Carter Farm and buildings in Archery: No. 1 - No. 4, 1976 December 18-24; (4 slide boxes) (Box 66)
      - A Tale of Two Williams, Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York
        - Renaissance Room with Joshua and Willie, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 67)
        - Joshua and the Christmas Tree, 1977 January 23; (2 slide boxes) (Box 67)
        - Joshua in the Museum store, 1977 January 13 (Box 67)
        - Joshua Link trying to open door in Egyptian Museum, 1977 January 31 (Box 67)
        - Joshua Link in the Egyptian Tomb, 1977 January 31 (Box 67)
        - Joshua Link -- going in and coming out of Tomb, 1977 January 31 (Box 67)
        - Joshua in the Mosque room, 1977 February 21 (Box 67)
        - The Armory, Joshua, 1977 February (Box 67)
        - Joshua arriving and leaving, 1977 February 21 (Box 67)
      - New York City, New York
        - Views of Manhattan from Paul Charlap's helicopter No. 1 - No. 2, 1976 September 12; (2 slide boxes) (Box 68)
        - New York City, South Street, Front Street, Peck Slip, 1979 May 5 (Box 68)
        - Con Edison Building, Peck Slip, and South Street, painted to create illusion of Brooklyn Bridge, 1979 May 28-29 (Box 68)
        - New York City from the World Trade Building, No. 1 - No. 3, 1980 April; (3 slide boxes) (Box 68)
        - Artist Richard Haas creates Times Building out of old Crossroads Building, NYC, 1980 April (Box 68)
        - New York City: Transit Strike, bicycles, Grand Central Station, Times Square signs, 1980 April (Box 68)
        - New York Book Festival, 5th Avenue, No. 1 - No. 2, 1985 September 22; (2 slide boxes) (Box 69)
        - Trompe l'Oeil -- fool the eye pictures 53rd street east of 3rd avenue between 2nd and 3rd, 1985 October 31 (Box 69)